My dear friend, you must be wondering
Amico mio, ti starai chiedendo
Why I'm leaving you a letter like this
perché ti sto lasciando questa lettera.
It's because...
È perché...
Hey, Gulab! I'm here. How are you feeling today?
Ehi, Gulab! Sono qui. Come ti senti oggi?
I gotta tell you, I had an idea for another card last night
Devo raccontarti l'idea che ho avuto per una nuova carta
Huh? What's that you're writing?
Eh? Che stai scrivendo?
Haha, it's nothing
Ahah, nulla di che.
Okay... Anyway, up for a game?
Ok... Comunque, ti va una partita?
You don't have to visit every day, you know. You should be focusing on your work at the Akademiya...
Non serve che mi visiti tutti i giorni, eh. Devi anche pensare al tuo lavoro all'Akademiya...
Hey, enough of that, I'll keep visiting until you've fully recovered
Ehi, smettila subito. Verrò a visitarti fino a che non ti sarai rimesso.
Besides, I can't stand most of the folks at the Akademiya anyway!
E poi, non sopporto quasi nessuno all'Akademiya!
Hey, it's your turn
Ehi, tocca a te.
*coughing*
*tossisce*
Gulab!? Are you okay?
Gulab!? Tutto bene?
*cough* Garvipidam, you must understand...
*tossisce* Garvipidam devi capire che...
My Eleazar...
il mio Eleazar...
Hey! Don't talk like that!
Ehi! Non dire così!
You just need some more rest...
Devi solo riposare ancora un po'...
*sigh*...
*sospira*
It's because... you won't come to terms with the fact that I don't have long left
È perché... non vuoi accettare che ormai mi resta poco.
Guess what? This game we invented
Lo sai? Il gioco che abbiamo inventato
Is getting pretty popular here in the hospital
sta diventando piuttosto famoso qui nell'ospedale.
Really? That's great news!
Davvero? Che bella notizia.
Yeah. I've even made a device
Già. Ho perfino costruito un dispositivo
To help people find other players nearby
per aiutare le persone a trovare giocatori nei dintorni.
Here, this one's for you
Ecco, questo è per te.
This way, you'll be able to keep playing even after I'm—
Così, potrai continuare a giocare anche dopo che sarò...
Just stop!
Basta!
You're gonna get better, you hear me? I don't need this thing... I don't want it!
Starai meglio, hai capito? Non mi serve quest'aggeggio... non lo voglio!
I imagine the Casket of Tomes I gave you
Suppongo che lo Scrigno degli arcani che ti ho dato
Is probably gathering dust in a corner somewhere...
stia facendo la polvere dimenticato da qualche parte...
So, this is my last gift to you. I'm sorry that I could only give it to you now
Quindi, questo è il mio ultimo regalo per te. Mi dispiace avertelo potuto dare solo ora.
Do you remember when we first met?
Ricordi quando ci siamo incontrati la prima volta?
You were the only one willing to be friends with the kid with Eleazar
Eri l'unico disposto a fare amicizia col bambino affetto da Eleazar.
Now it's my turn to help you make some new friends
Ora tocca a me aiutarti a fare nuove amicizie.
This way, I'll always be by your side, my friend
Così facendo, sarò sempre al tuo fianco, amico mio.